{
    "id": "a47dcadfca4148d483707f8a68691c07",
    "title": "General Vocabulary Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It was such a ………………. state of affairs that we had to laugh.",
            "description": "Comic / comical – funny, humorous, laughable",
            "answers": [
                "comic",
                "categorical",
                "brazen"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The senator’s ………………… made him intolerant of other countries.",
            "description": "Chauvinism – super patriotism",
            "answers": [
                "brashness",
                "stupidity",
                "chauvinism"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher ………………… the child for arriving late.",
            "description": "To chastise is to punish or scold. All of these words mean the same.",
            "answers": [
                "chastised",
                "reprimanded",
                "censured",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Without rules, people would live in a state of ……………….",
            "description": "Chaos – turmoil, upheaval, confusion",
            "answers": [
                "chaos",
                "harmony",
                "bungle"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The minister made a ………………….. denial of the charges that he had taken bribes.",
            "description": "Categorical – absolute, unconditional",
            "answers": [
                "brazen",
                "categorical",
                "brash"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The plumber …………………. the job and now the pipe leaks.",
            "description": "Bungle – do badly, make a mess of",
            "answers": [
                "bungled",
                "abashed",
                "chastised"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How can you believe such a ………………….. lie?",
            "description": "Brazen – impudent, shameless",
            "answers": [
                "brazen",
                "white",
                "sordid"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Buying the house without having it appraised was …………………",
            "description": "Brash – rash, reckless, careless",
            "answers": [
                "brazen",
                "brash",
                "impudent"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is important to ............................. with those in trouble to really understand their suffering.",
            "description": "To empathize is to share the feelings of another person.",
            "answers": [
                "empathize",
                "emote",
                "devise"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The spy checked into the hotel under a ............................ name.",
            "description": "Fictitious - unreal or false",
            "answers": [
                "figurative",
                "fictitious",
                "alien"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}